If I see that woman
anywhere near our house,
I'll make her pay for this.
So annoying!
Hannah Montano!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Good to see
that you're still here.
Where's your bag?
Why, ma'am?
Miss Ria lost her jewelry.
You two were the only ones
in the presidential suite.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We weren't the only ones there.
The security already
cleared Miss Brenda.
Ma'am, wait.
Hannah is not a thief.
Do you want to get involved?
No.
- It's all right, Katy.
- Hannah.
I have nothing to be ashamed of.
I'm not hiding anything.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Well, well, well...
The former social climber...
is now a kleptomaniac!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
So pretty!
Very fresh!
Yes!
She's so pretty. Yes!
You're glowing! Wow!
Go on, pose some more.
To the right, to the left.
Oh, she's posing.
Yes. Beautiful!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]